<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='yes'?>
<list>
<doc id='Afghanistan'>In the country Afghanistan in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Afghan Persian, Dari, Pashtu, Turkic languages, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Albania'>In the country Albania in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Albanian, Greek, Vlach, Romani, Slavic dialects.</doc>
<doc id='Algeria'>In the country Algeria in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, French, Berber dialects.</doc>
<doc id='Andorra'>In the country Andorra in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Catalan, French, Castilian Spanish, Portuguese.</doc>
<doc id='Angola'>In the country Angola in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Portuguese, Bantu, African languages.</doc>
<doc id='Antigua and Barbuda'>In the country Antigua and Barbuda in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, local dialects.</doc>
<doc id='Argentina'>In the country Argentina in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, English, Italian, German, French.</doc>
<doc id='Armenia'>In the country Armenia in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Armenian, Yezidi, Russian.</doc>
<doc id='Australia'>In the country Australia in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Chinese, Italian, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Austria'>In the country Austria in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: German, Slovene, Croatian, Hungarian.</doc>
<doc id='Azerbaijan'>In the country Azerbaijan in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Azerbaijani, Russian, Armenian, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Bahamas'>In the country Bahamas in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Creole.</doc>
<doc id='Bahrain'>In the country Bahrain in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, English, Farsi, Urdu.</doc>
<doc id='Bangladesh'>In the country Bangladesh in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Bengali, English.</doc>
<doc id='Barbados'>In the country Barbados in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English.</doc>
<doc id='Belarus'>In the country Belarus in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Belarusian, Russian, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Belgium'>In the country Belgium in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Dutch, French, German.</doc>
<doc id='Belize'>In the country Belize in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Spanish, Mayan, Garifuna, Creole.</doc>
<doc id='Benin'>In the country Benin in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Fon and Yoruba, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Bhutan'>In the country Bhutan in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Dzongkha, Tibetan, Nepalese.</doc>
<doc id='Bolivia'>In the country Bolivia in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, Quechua, Aymara.</doc>
<doc id='Bosnia and Herzegovina'>In the country Bosnia and Herzegovina in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Bosnian, Croatian, Serbian.</doc>
<doc id='Botswana'>In the country Botswana in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Setswana, Kalanga, Sekgalagadi, English.</doc>
<doc id='Brazil'>In the country Brazil in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Portuguese, Spanish, English, French.</doc>
<doc id='Brunei'>In the country Brunei in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Malay, English, Chinese.</doc>
<doc id='Bulgaria'>In the country Bulgaria in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Bulgarian, Turkish, Roma.</doc>
<doc id='Burkina Faso'>In the country Burkina Faso in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, African languages.</doc>
<doc id='Burundi'>In the country Burundi in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Kirundi, French, Swahili.</doc>
<doc id='Cambodia'>In the country Cambodia in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Khmer, French, English.</doc>
<doc id='Cameroon'>In the country Cameroon in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: African languages, English, French.</doc>
<doc id='Canada'>In the country Canada in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, French, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Cape Verde'>In the country Cape Verde in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Portuguese, Crioulo.</doc>
<doc id='Central African Republic'>In the country Central African Republic in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Sangho, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Chad'>In the country Chad in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Arabic, Sara, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Chile'>In the country Chile in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish.</doc>
<doc id='China'>In the country China in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Mandarin, Yue, Wu, Minbei, Minnan, Xiang, Gan, Hakka dialects, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Colombia'>In the country Colombia in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish.</doc>
<doc id='Comoros'>In the country Comoros in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, French, Shikomoro.</doc>
<doc id='Congo'>In the country Congo in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Lingala, Kingwana, Kikongo, Tshiluba, Monokutuba, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Cook Islands'>In the country Cook Islands in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Maori.</doc>
<doc id='Costa Rica'>In the country Costa Rica in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, English.</doc>
<doc id='Cote d&quot;Ivoire'>In the country Cote d&quot;Ivoire in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Dioula and native dialects.</doc>
<doc id='Croatia'>In the country Croatia in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Croatian, Serbian, Italian, Hungarian, Czech, Slovak, German.</doc>
<doc id='Cuba'>In the country Cuba in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish.</doc>
<doc id='Cyprus'>In the country Cyprus in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Greek, Turkish, English.</doc>
<doc id='Czech Republic'>In the country Czech Republic in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Czech.</doc>
<doc id='Denmark'>In the country Denmark in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Danish, Faroese, Greenlandic, German; English.</doc>
<doc id='Djibouti'>In the country Djibouti in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Arabic, Somali, Afar.</doc>
<doc id='Dominica'>In the country Dominica in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, French patois.</doc>
<doc id='Dominican Republic'>In the country Dominican Republic in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish.</doc>
<doc id='East Timor'>In the country East Timor in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Tetum, Portuguese, Indonesian, English, Galole, Mambae, Kemak.</doc>
<doc id='Ecuador'>In the country Ecuador in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, Amerindian languages.</doc>
<doc id='Egypt'>In the country Egypt in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, English and French.</doc>
<doc id='El Salvador'>In the country El Salvador in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, Nahua.</doc>
<doc id='Equatorial Guinea'>In the country Equatorial Guinea in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, French, pidgin English, Fang, Bubi, Ibo.</doc>
<doc id='Eritrea'>In the country Eritrea in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Afar, Arabic, Tigre, Kunama, Tigrinya, Cushitic languages.</doc>
<doc id='Estonia'>In the country Estonia in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Estonian, Russian.</doc>
<doc id='Ethiopia'>In the country Ethiopia in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Amharic, Tigrinya, Oromigna, Guaragigna, Somali, Arabic, local languages, English.</doc>
<doc id='Fiji'>In the country Fiji in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Fijian, Hindustani.</doc>
<doc id='Finland'>In the country Finland in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Finnish, Swedish, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='France'>In the country France in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Provencal, Breton, Alsatian, Corsican, Catalan, Basque, Flemish.</doc>
<doc id='French Guiana'>In the country French Guiana in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: French.</doc>
<doc id='Gabon'>In the country Gabon in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Fang, Myene, Nzebi, Bapounou, Bapounou, Eschira, Bandjabi.</doc>
<doc id='Gambia'>In the country Gambia in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Mandinka, Wolof, Fula, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Gaza Strip'>In the country Gaza Strip in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, Hebrew, English.</doc>
<doc id='Georgia'>In the country Georgia in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Georgian, Russian, Armenian, Azeri, Abkhaz, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Germany'>In the country Germany in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: German.</doc>
<doc id='Ghana'>In the country Ghana in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Akan, Moshi- Moshi-Dagomba, Ewe, Ga.</doc>
<doc id='Greece'>In the country Greece in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Greek, English, French.</doc>
<doc id='Grenada'>In the country Grenada in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, French patois.</doc>
<doc id='Guatemala'>In the country Guatemala in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, Quiche, Cakchiquel, Kekchi, Mam, Garifuna, Xinca.</doc>
<doc id='Guinea'>In the country Guinea in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Guinea-Bissau'>In the country Guinea-Bissau in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Portuguese, Crioulo, African languages.</doc>
<doc id='Guyana'>In the country Guyana in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Amerindian dialects, Creole, Hindi, Urdu.</doc>
<doc id='Haiti'>In the country Haiti in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Creole.</doc>
<doc id='Honduras'>In the country Honduras in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, Amerindian dialects.</doc>
<doc id='Hong Kong'>In the country Hong Kong in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Chinese, English;.</doc>
<doc id='Hungary'>In the country Hungary in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Hungarian.</doc>
<doc id='Iceland'>In the country Iceland in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Icelandic, English, Nordic languages; German.</doc>
<doc id='India'>In the country India in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Hindi, English, Bengali, Telugu, Marathi, Tamil, Urdu, Gujarati, Malayalam, Kannada, Oriya, Punjabi, Assamese, Kashmiri, Sindhi, Sanskrit; Hindustani, Urdu.</doc>
<doc id='Indonesia'>In the country Indonesia in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Bahasa Indonesia, English, Dutch, Javanese.</doc>
<doc id='Iran'>In the country Iran in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Persian and Persian dialects, Turkic and Turkic dialects, Kurdish, Luri, Balochi, Arabic, Turkish, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Iraq'>In the country Iraq in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, Kurdish, Assyrian, Armenian.</doc>
<doc id='Ireland'>In the country Ireland in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Irish Gaelic.</doc>
<doc id='Israel'>In the country Israel in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Hebrew, Arabic, English.</doc>
<doc id='Italy'>In the country Italy in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Italian, German, French, Slovene.</doc>
<doc id='Jamaica'>In the country Jamaica in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, English patois.</doc>
<doc id='Japan'>In the country Japan in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Japanese.</doc>
<doc id='Jordan'>In the country Jordan in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic; English.</doc>
<doc id='Kazakhstan'>In the country Kazakhstan in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Kazakh, Russian.</doc>
<doc id='Kenya'>In the country Kenya in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Kiswahili, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Kiribati'>In the country Kiribati in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: I- I-Kiribati, English.</doc>
<doc id='Korea, North'>In the country Korea, North in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Korean;.</doc>
<doc id='Korea, South'>In the country Korea, South in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Korean; English.</doc>
<doc id='Kosovo'>In the country Kosovo in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Albanian, Serbian, Bosnian, Turkish, Gorani, Romani.</doc>
<doc id='Kuwait'>In the country Kuwait in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic; English.</doc>
<doc id='Kyrgyzstan'>In the country Kyrgyzstan in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Kyrgyz, Russian.</doc>
<doc id='Laos'>In the country Laos in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Lao, French, English, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Latvia'>In the country Latvia in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Latvian, Russian, Lithuanian, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Lebanon'>In the country Lebanon in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, French, English, Armenian.</doc>
<doc id='Lesotho'>In the country Lesotho in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Sesotho, English, Zulu, Xhosa.</doc>
<doc id='Liberia'>In the country Liberia in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Libya'>In the country Libya in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, Italian, English.</doc>
<doc id='Liechtenstein'>In the country Liechtenstein in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: German, Alemannic dialect.</doc>
<doc id='Lithuania'>In the country Lithuania in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Lithuanian, Russian, Polish.</doc>
<doc id='Luxembourg'>In the country Luxembourg in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Luxembourgish, German, French.</doc>
<doc id='Macau'>In the country Macau in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Cantonese, Hokkien, Mandarin, Chinese dialects, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Macedonia'>In the country Macedonia in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Macedonian, Albanian, Turkish, Roma, Serbian, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Madagascar'>In the country Madagascar in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Malagasy.</doc>
<doc id='Malawi'>In the country Malawi in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Chichewa, Chinyanja, Chiyao, Chitumbuka, Chisena, Chilomwe, Chitonga, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Malaysia'>In the country Malaysia in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Bahasa Melayu, English, Mandarin, Cantonese, Hokkien, Hakka, Hainan, Foochow, Tamil, Telugu, Malayalam, Panjabi, Thai.</doc>
<doc id='Maldives'>In the country Maldives in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Maldivian Dhivehi, English.</doc>
<doc id='Mali'>In the country Mali in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Bambara, African languages.</doc>
<doc id='Malta'>In the country Malta in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Maltese, English.</doc>
<doc id='Marshall Islands'>In the country Marshall Islands in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Marshallese, English.</doc>
<doc id='Mauritania'>In the country Mauritania in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, Pulaar, Soninke, French, Hassaniya, Wolof.</doc>
<doc id='Mauritius'>In the country Mauritius in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Creole, Bhojpuri, French, English.</doc>
<doc id='Mexico'>In the country Mexico in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, Mayan, Nahuatl, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Micronesia'>In the country Micronesia in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Trukese, Pohnpeian, Yapese, Kosrean, Ulithian, Woleaian, Nukuoro, Kapingamarangi.</doc>
<doc id='Moldova'>In the country Moldova in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Moldovan, Russian, Gagauz.</doc>
<doc id='Monaco'>In the country Monaco in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, English, Italian, Monegasque.</doc>
<doc id='Mongolia'>In the country Mongolia in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Khalkha Mongol, Turkic, Russian.</doc>
<doc id='Montenegro'>In the country Montenegro in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Serbian.</doc>
<doc id='Morocco'>In the country Morocco in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, Berber dialects, French.</doc>
<doc id='Mozambique'>In the country Mozambique in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Emakhuwa, Xichangana, Portuguese, Elomwe, Cisena, Echuwabo, Mozambican languages, English, Afrikaans, German, Oshivambo, Herero, Nama.</doc>
<doc id='Myanmar'>In the country Myanmar in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Burmese, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Namibia'>In the country Namibia in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Afrikaans, Dama/Nama, German, Herero, Oshiwambo, Rukwangali, Setswana, Silozi.</doc>
<doc id='Nauru'>In the country Nauru in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Nauruan.</doc>
<doc id='Nepal'>In the country Nepal in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Nepali, Maithali, Bhojpuri, Tharu, Tamang, Newar, Magar, Awadhi, English.</doc>
<doc id='Netherlands'>In the country Netherlands in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Dutch, Frisian.</doc>
<doc id='New Zealand'>In the country New Zealand in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Maori.</doc>
<doc id='Nicaragua'>In the country Nicaragua in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, Miskito; English and local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Niger'>In the country Niger in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Hausa, Djerma.</doc>
<doc id='Nigeria'>In the country Nigeria in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Hausa, Yoruba, Igbo, Fulani.</doc>
<doc id='Niue'>In the country Niue in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Niuean, English.</doc>
<doc id='Norway'>In the country Norway in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Norwegian, Sami, Finnish; Sami, Finnish.</doc>
<doc id='Oman'>In the country Oman in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, English, Baluchi, Urdu, Indian dialects.</doc>
<doc id='Pakistan'>In the country Pakistan in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Punjabi, Sindhi, Siraiki, Pashtu, Urdu, Balochi, Hindko, Brahui, English, Burushaski, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Palau'>In the country Palau in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Palauan, Angaur, Filipino, English, Chinese, Carolinian, Japanese.</doc>
<doc id='Panama'>In the country Panama in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, English.</doc>
<doc id='Papua New Guinea'>In the country Papua New Guinea in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Melanesian Pidgin, English, Motu; local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Paraguay'>In the country Paraguay in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, Guarani.</doc>
<doc id='Peru'>In the country Peru in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, Quechua, Aymara, Amazonian languages.</doc>
<doc id='Philippines'>In the country Philippines in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Tagalog, English, Cebuano, Ilocano, Hiligaynon or Ilonggo, Bicol, Waray, Pampango, Pangasinan.</doc>
<doc id='Poland'>In the country Poland in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Polish.</doc>
<doc id='Portugal'>In the country Portugal in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Portuguese, Mirandese.</doc>
<doc id='Qatar'>In the country Qatar in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic; English.</doc>
<doc id='Romania'>In the country Romania in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Romanian, Hungarian, German.</doc>
<doc id='Russia'>In the country Russia in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Russian, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Rwanda'>In the country Rwanda in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Kinyarwanda, French, English, Kiswahili.</doc>
<doc id='Saint Kitts and Nevis'>In the country Saint Kitts and Nevis in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English.</doc>
<doc id='Saint Lucia'>In the country Saint Lucia in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, French patois.</doc>
<doc id='Saint Vincent and the Grenadines'>In the country Saint Vincent and the Grenadines in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, French patois.</doc>
<doc id='Samoa'>In the country Samoa in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Samoan, English.</doc>
<doc id='San Marino'>In the country San Marino in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Italian.</doc>
<doc id='Sao Tome and Principe'>In the country Sao Tome and Principe in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Portuguese.</doc>
<doc id='Saudi Arabia'>In the country Saudi Arabia in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic.</doc>
<doc id='Senegal'>In the country Senegal in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Wolof, Pulaar, Jola, Mandinka.</doc>
<doc id='Serbia'>In the country Serbia in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Serbian, Romanian, Hungarian, Slovak, Ukrainian, Croatian.</doc>
<doc id='Seychelles'>In the country Seychelles in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Creole, English.</doc>
<doc id='Sierra Leone'>In the country Sierra Leone in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Mende, Temne, Krio.</doc>
<doc id='Singapore'>In the country Singapore in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Mandarin, English, Malay, Hokkien, Cantonese, Teochew, Tamil, Chinese dialects, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Slovakia'>In the country Slovakia in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Slovak, Hungarian, Roma, Ukrainian.</doc>
<doc id='Slovenia'>In the country Slovenia in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Slovenian, Serbo-Croatian.</doc>
<doc id='Solomon Islands'>In the country Solomon Islands in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Melanesian pidgin, English; local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Somalia'>In the country Somalia in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Somali, Arabic, Italian, English.</doc>
<doc id='South Africa'>In the country South Africa in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: IsiZulu, IsiXhosa, Afrikaans, Sepedi, English, Setswana, Sesotho, Xitsonga, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Spain'>In the country Spain in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Castilian Spanish, Catalan, Galician, Basque.</doc>
<doc id='Sri Lanka'>In the country Sri Lanka in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Sinhala, Tamil, local languages; English.</doc>
<doc id='Sudan'>In the country Sudan in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, Nubian, Ta Bedawie, Nilotic languages, Nilo-Hamitic languages, Sudanic languages, English.</doc>
<doc id='Suriname'>In the country Suriname in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Dutch, English, Sranang Tongo, Sranang Tongo, Hindustani, Javanese.</doc>
<doc id='Swaziland'>In the country Swaziland in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, siSwati.</doc>
<doc id='Sweden'>In the country Sweden in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Swedish, Sami, Finnish.</doc>
<doc id='Switzerland'>In the country Switzerland in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: German, French, Italian, Serbo-Croatian, Albanian, Portuguese, Spanish, English, Romansch, local languages; German, French, Italian, and Romansch.</doc>
<doc id='Syria'>In the country Syria in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, Kurdish, Armenian, Aramaic, Circassian, French, English.</doc>
<doc id='Taiwan'>In the country Taiwan in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Mandarin Chinese, Taiwanese, Hakka dialects.</doc>
<doc id='Tajikistan'>In the country Tajikistan in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Tajik, Russian.</doc>
<doc id='Tanzania'>In the country Tanzania in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Kiswahili or Swahili, Kiunguja, English, Arabic.</doc>
<doc id='Thailand'>In the country Thailand in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Thai, English.</doc>
<doc id='Togo'>In the country Togo in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: French, Ewe and Mina, Kabye.</doc>
<doc id='Tonga'>In the country Tonga in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Tongan, English.</doc>
<doc id='Trinidad and Tobago'>In the country Trinidad and Tobago in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Hindi, French, Spanish, Chinese.</doc>
<doc id='Tunisia'>In the country Tunisia in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, French.</doc>
<doc id='Turkey'>In the country Turkey in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Turkish, Kurdish, Dimli, Azeri, Kabardian; Gagauz.</doc>
<doc id='Turkmenistan'>In the country Turkmenistan in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Turkmen, Russian, Uzbek, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Tuvalu'>In the country Tuvalu in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Tuvaluan, English, Samoan, Kiribati.</doc>
<doc id='Uganda'>In the country Uganda in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Ganda or Luganda, Niger-Congo languages, Nilo-Saharan languages, Swahili, Arabic.</doc>
<doc id='Ukraine'>In the country Ukraine in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Ukrainian, Russian, Romanian, Polish, Hungarian.</doc>
<doc id='United Arab Emirates'>In the country United Arab Emirates in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic, Persian, English, Hindi, Urdu.</doc>
<doc id='United Kingdom'>In the country United Kingdom in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Welsh, Scottish Gaelic.</doc>
<doc id='United States of America'>In the country United States of America in <continent id='North and Central America'>North and Central America</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Spanish, Native American local languages; Indo-European, Asian and Pacific island languages are spoken.</doc>
<doc id='Uruguay'>In the country Uruguay in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, Portunol, Brazilero.</doc>
<doc id='Uzbekistan'>In the country Uzbekistan in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Uzbek, Russian, Tajik, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Vanuatu'>In the country Vanuatu in <continent id='Oceania/Australia'>Oceania/Australia</continent> are the following languages spoken: local languages, pidgin, English, French.</doc>
<doc id='Vatican City'>In the country Vatican City in <continent id='Europe'>Europe</continent> are the following languages spoken: Italian, Latin, French.</doc>
<doc id='Venezuela'>In the country Venezuela in <continent id='South America'>South America</continent> are the following languages spoken: Spanish, local dialects.</doc>
<doc id='Vietnam'>In the country Vietnam in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Vietnamese, French, English, Chinese, Khmer, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Western Sahara'>In the country Western Sahara in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: Hassaniya Arabic, Moroccan Arabic.</doc>
<doc id='Yemen'>In the country Yemen in <continent id='Asia'>Asia</continent> are the following languages spoken: Arabic.</doc>
<doc id='Zambia'>In the country Zambia in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Bemba, Kaonda, Lozi, Lunda, Luvale, Nyanja, Tonga, local languages.</doc>
<doc id='Zimbabwe'>In the country Zimbabwe in <continent id='Africa'>Africa</continent> are the following languages spoken: English, Shona, Sindebele.</doc>
</list>
